twenty19.com 2010-08-06

# Search, apply for, internships, summer internships, summer projects, summer training, internships in india, chennai, bangalore, delhi, pune, hyderabad, kolkata, mumbai. Virtual internships, work form home

## Overview

We strongly respect your privacy and strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth our online data collection and usage policies and practices. By using our services, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement.

Your data will be stored and processed in or outside and your usage of the site constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of India. Our site may contain links to other website over which we have no control and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to link from the website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information we collect on twenty19.com and not to information collected otherwise.

## Collection and Retention of Information

In some areas of our websites we request you to provide or submit personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. Twenty19 also collects or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your ZIP code, age, preferences and gender. Example of such a situation could be when you sign up to use our service, post a resume or enter a contest or survey. In addition we may indirectly collect information about you when you use certain third party services on our website; such information will be subject to, and treated in accordance with, the policies and practices described in this Statement.

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our site, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by us. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.

Twenty19 may sometimes afford you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioral and preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. If you do provide such information, you are thereby consenting to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Statement. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services.

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of Twenty19.com, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom Twenty19 has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of this website.

Since we believe that managing your career is a life-long process, we retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use with us more efficient, practical, and relevant. Of course, you can correct or update your account profile and resume at any time. Moreover, you can delete your resume from our online database or close your account at any time, in which event we will remove all our copies of your resume and your account profile information except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the internet.

## Children

Twenty19 is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

## Cookies

Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us.

## No Guarantees

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of data.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact us at [info@twenty19.com](mailto:info@twenty19.com "Contact Us")
